hcareers.ca 2006-06-15

# Hcareers - Privacy Commitment

"Hcareers pledges its commitment to protecting the privacy of our users."

  * Information Disclosure
  * Visitor Information
  * Resumes
  * To Update Your Account
  * Cookies
  * Feedback
  * Private Label Sites
  * Children
  * Changes to our Privacy Commitment
  * General

**Information Disclosure**

Except as described in this privacy policy, we do not use or disclose, to any outside parties, any personal information that you provide, such as your name, e-mail address, telephone number, and employment information, except when we are permitted or required by law, including the Personal Information Protection Act (British Columbia) and other applicable privacy laws. We do not sell, rent or exchange lists of job seekers or employers with other companies.

We do employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf, e.g. web site development. These other companies will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions on our behalf, but they may not share that information with any third party or otherwise use that information.

When you sign up to use a service of Hcareers, we may use that information to administer and build your Hcareers’ account, to provide the services that you have requested, to understand the needs of our clients and to ensure a high standard of service to our clients, and we may make it available to employers and recruiters in connection with those services. We may also use that information to make you aware of additional news and services that may be of interest to you. You may choose to opt out of receiving these additional news and services by replying to the notice and instructing us to remove you from further notices.

**Visitor Information**

Hcareers monitors our website visitor information, such as which pages you visit most frequently and which site referred you. This data does not include any personally identifying information. We use this information in order to optimize our website and to assess its usage. We may provide such information to our website contractors for these purposes.

**Resumes**

To help you find or apply to jobs, Hcareers gives you the option of putting your resume in our database. You can either store your resume in our database, but not allow it to be searchable by employers (which means that you use it only apply to specific jobs online), or you can allow your resume to be searchable by all employers and recruiters who pay for access to our resume database.

Please know that we use our best efforts to grant access to our resume database only to paying employers and recruiters, but we cannot guarantee that other parties will not, without our consent, gain access to this database. You may remove your resume at any time, but know that anyone (authorized or unauthorized) who has had access to our database may have retained a copy of your resume. Please know that we are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of resumes in these instances, or for the use or privacy of resumes by any of such parties while resumes are in the database.

**To Update Your Account**

To update your personal information at any time on Hcareers, please log-in to your account and go to the "User Options" where you may edit your information.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies for remembering your user names and passwords etc. Cookies enable us to understand how our site is used and to make improvements. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies, but this will negatively impact your experience on our site.

**Feedback**

Hcareers allows you to submit feedback to us. This feedback becomes the property of Hcareers and we may use this feedback for marketing, e.g. success stories.

**Private Label Sites**

Hcareers hosts private label employment sites (Custom Job Banks) on behalf of other companies and permits online applications to job postings. All online applications to job postings on a private label site are placed directly into the employers' Hcareers Inbox to be viewed by anyone privy to or who otherwise gains access to the employers Hcareers User Id & password. Please know that we are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of information accessed by others through Custom Job Banks or online applications to job postings. 

**Children**

Hcareers does not collect information about children and further believes that children should get their parents' consent before giving out personal information. If you are concerned about this, we encourage you to use web filtering technology to supervise your child's access to the site.

**Changes to our Privacy Commitment**

Any changes to our Privacy Commitment will be posted here and will be effective upon posting. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about Hcareers' privacy commitment, please feel free to e-mail us at [privacy@hcareers.com](mailto:privacy@hcareers.com). 

**General**

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies or other entities that Hcareers does not manage or control. This privacy policy does not apply to information regarding corporations or other non-individuals. We cannot guarantee the confidentiality or security of any information sent by you to us via the website. 

This privacy policy will be governed by the laws of the Province of British Columbia and the laws of Canada applicable therein, excluding any conflict of laws rules that would apply another body of law. This privacy policy constitutes and contains the entire agreement between you and Hcareers with respect to its subject matter and supersedes any prior oral or written agreements.

If any provision of this privacy policy is held to be illegal or unenforceable, that provision will be limited or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary so that this privacy policy will otherwise remaining full force and effect and enforceable.

Thank you again for using Hcareers - "The most restaurant & hospitality jobs ... anywhere!"
